Louis.
Louis Leakey.
Louis
Leakey or Louis.
Louis. Louis.
Louis. Louis if
you want to. Yes monsieur and I
think you remember. Him. Well.
I've been studying painting with you some
time now. Do you think it's worth my
while to go on what I need
a way that is what I feel is no sense of
my staying in this I have talent if you
are not certain about your talent why did
you stay on come out because all this he
said of me so beautiful to me in my youth
it was also beautiful to me but now that
is the city I've lost evolution in and you
did your bidding are no no hey let's go
there you will show me what you
have done Janja in the in the.
Have you any money and little
not enough to live on.
Then I must tell you there is no talent
here neatly industry ending television. You
will never be anything but mediocre and
it is very cruel to discover one's
mediocrity only when it
is too late. I know.
The see that that name does not belong
there it belongs somewhere else. Take your
courage in both your hands and
make something of your life.
If you anything in mind when
you see. I have my limitations
my father was
a doctor I've always been interested in
medicine and if I can be great. At least
one can be of some use to people.
You.
Know like that such a thing
upon my time never had
a day to loosen my knife and
that is what we call in a couple
a great many middle aged women
have a. Thing to say to
a lady no one's ever called me middle
aged it's all time you got used to.
Say the same to you good day Madam That'll
be all now rest you come back tomorrow
getting ready.
You're the boy's father yes.
What's the matter with you.
You see well enough of the
matter is the boy has
a clubfoot Oh. Can't you better take this
case it's up to your to know something
but.
It's only for the looks of the thing you
know I don't find it no trouble don't you
that's wonderful. I always
did. You seem to be
a little slow OK I think
I'll have to instruct
a class but many of the writers of coffee
this is one of the less interesting.
Yours would probably prove more interesting
you have to let your Queen of Heaven go
yes I believe my take
over sock to you Carrie.
No How soon.
Keep you speak nice and clean doesn T.
. Yes just as I thought tell
a pizza queen that malformation requiring
you to walk on the outside to put
a very interesting example I
must say you mind of having
a. Congenital Clubfoot in simple language
a foot twisted in would the cause of
this twisting is not clear hereditary
inference plays
a part here as pointed out by Dr Little who
traces recurring deformity through four
generations and when you've
quite finished. I say
Oh man I like that. French isn't the issue
with love in Paris you know I can't for
the not in the understand why you gave up
painting. I'd rather look at that all day
long than of this. WOMAN You know you can
tell by the hell this. I like and with
a little more. Of their
life in the old girl you
don't inhale the. I say I'm going to be
getting along it's a little matter of
a balmy at the Crown and Anchor and very
nice to chilly out funny fellow is me
I say carry him must mean wonderful having
that night in Paris and you mean that
you really knew all those fascinating women
oh some of them I feel just the man I'm
looking for I wonder if you couldn't
help me in my way well there's
a girl and I can't get anywhere with her
and you've been to Paris and all that I'm
sure you could say something
that would give me
a starter I don't ask Griffith only he
couldn't do it and remember who he was doing
it for you are just the next
you know something to make
a law. But you don't
believe you are doing it and.
I say She's marvelous
isn't. She didn't need.
It. You don't suppose she likes that
down to Do you cook Now's
your chance to say something.
But I see your friends going I don't know
what you mean. I was referring to the
nobleman with the Sandinista. As he
let you have another. Some people
would do better to mind
their own business. By.
A nice back amount speaking terms with your
back when you know. You can tell by the
television. And that. Calls
in some particular. I
apologize Well Paul I promised you something
charming and she turned up B.O.H.
And contemptible I'm sorry that you employed
all that's all right you don't suppose
I care what you need me couldn't we just
need to well I do. Good I must be going
coming along. No I think
I'll have some more tea.
Anything you want to. Get them
out I told you. And. You'll be
aware that it. Makes no difference to me
I have to be here all day or don't write
that I don't want to sit on the present.
Day and say that. You know you have
a lovely smile you should use more of it
don't go spit be. That it works hard all
day like I do don't have much reason
to smile. That's I could find
a reason. We don't let me try. That I know
where the wrong but you know whether I
well I hope you decide you will.
I mean.
Like when I got my job. I know.
That if
a nice to have. You
. Give me what you know.
How to Do You seem to be in
a great honey waiting ten
minutes. You know you could drop
in here that look to be Looks like you don't
know if we could look at it that way.
You are strange so. I say when you
die meet on time and we've got
a better. Idea behind when
you come I'm OK but I chose
a thirty seven o'clockne Toria station.
All right I'm eager to toil in the costly.
Fall they say you know they're.
Going. To get. Right back oh
Nike. Olympic athlete. Yellow Jacket. They
may. All to they. All
say they can all take
a long way to. Go along to. Take
a three. Year old to. Take
a leap. Right that long
ninety year old think they.
Really thought you're never coming up like
that after keeping me waiting I almost
went home I was in the second class waiting
and I thought you said you'd be there
now I say you did lucky on the second pass
my kids in the first. I didn't in the
base jump you think to me. That's not
any way you hear their story and it
certainly do make again
important to. I love that you.
Whenever I hear you. OK the.
Strain of code. You
are giving. You
a little. Know why you do it now.
I was hoping to make you
look and. You think it will.
Be one thing I can see believe.
Temptingly every six who will.
Be.
Back here again I don't mind. Doesn't
make any difference to me. Now.
You gotta take me out come on
a train or. Eat. I
think the night. Wednesday from now on one
of our people will think I don't know
what.
You know now that you. Never
hear it I think you never.
Think about it.
You. Have.
Never done any. Damage
to. The I mean the view.
Of My Life.
Yes teams have let's do
a good time when I should be
study and why don't. You. And
if. I don't know I want to make.
It to you now or do they.
Now call you militant. And. Say that.
I know well let's head out.
And you call me. I think.
I am. I'm
a little awkward at this. We
have kissed me good night net. I
don't mind.
My name is Miller and we'll build up we
should know each other why we are both
interested in the same thing. Thing
my dear young man you so do.
I just think you should be bar.
Like the whole thing thanks
very much that. That's
all right. To change.
What times I see you. Take it up
a cock and. Why not me on the.
Process ends in that yes because I want to
give out myself to you only got them yes
Say what you mean go on about.
Why. You. Keep. Your spying
on me I was off he was
a gentleman in every sense of the
way. Are you going out with Mila now.
We have what if I am going to go
out with him I want to come down.
To be waiting in the way and I'd rather
wait to hear. If you wait for me.
But you change your mind I'll get
some more tickets and will now.
You keep looking for him
the way I look to you.
If you don't come after me tonight you'll
never see me again good riddance to bad
bout it.
Thank.
You.
Thought oh boy. How about
a nice be it. Wouldn't
help. Or what would.
You.
Give me. My luck book
shows the way we are.
You know who you are. And. What you
mean. I'm sorry and you're
a bit just a few mean
a fine young painter. Moving.
Because you know like me and
a cripple can get to the
cattle it alone. Killing. My
my. You are in.
Your OP you're not you don't
know what you're doing what's on
a practice can you expect to have with
a wife like that I don't know let me ask
you something why do you want to marry
this guy. Because I'm so
in love with the opposite.
That ring with
a little design very popular we
celebrate many of them that he. Can
think of it. When we surprise
our baby in the night.
I was delighted when Yeah yeah. Why but I
don't know what humans are sweet to me
all day I guess I mean to ask you and it
makes it so much easier for me next easier
for me to. On something to
change and let me tend to.
That is. I want you to marry
me. It's just hard and it.
Just when I was about ten
you. Waited so long. It is.
Going to be married. By you. To
whom and then on now. And then
a good money. Being spent. I'm
sure. Why you want to go on about
it when you're. Getting on trying to fall
Thomason down. And winning fifty pounds
when he got good prospects. Looks good bomb
I hate it Montana that Ladan
gauge I'm going to hit
a real dent and I'm going to Mitt.
Romney. Winning on. The one
hand. In the in the.
Other that I.
You know. No. Well. In the world and you
know the Q. Of
a one woman another right. And
. Meat don't.
You know did that junk you. Know
I write it. That hired my living
I didn't and successful marriage
I have an image popularity of
a kitchen maid and they
picked the cellar of our.
Best out on the up there
eat. This talk about us.
Not to. Get rid of front
of me and you. Clever boy
your outfit Mulisch pressed. Oh my dear
never struck me that you could make. A life
. So proud so every inch of. So great
and I wish you hadn't been in love with
meat but wasn't. Mildred. Going to
she had occasion to go down and
they. Wouldn't thank you
so long to understand her.
Me me me. Me me me me me.
Me I saw you. I want
a quick. Let's go out and say. I'm your
past Saturday.
Morning at. Hand.
The one. In.
The middle you want what you get out. Me
you'll never know if they don't get much
on me. I wish me only I
could take you dancing.
I know how you love it they really are going
to be so sensitive about you but. You
know other people don't think about it
nearly as much as you do. They know that
when they both you and after that they
forget all about you eat. You know
I only speak of it because I know you and
I don't want to make one happy. Hour you
please stay here and go on
cramming for that if there.
Is
a ninety two C.D.'s or is that I shouldn't
have let you know that she was the tops
and you are.
What you want. I didn't think
I'd ever see you again.
America. He left me. In.
So heavy. If. I'm going to
have
a baby. Right
you see down.
There you want him back. He'll never
come back why not. He just won't.
Go is why he has to provide
for you he won't give me any.
Even if he did I wouldn't take it why not.
You know what happened I've still got me
pride. That's something
and then. You got the
money. To help. Really better get yourself
a place to live after
everything will be done. And
you always feel good to me that's
why I knew I could come to you.
Now look at Mr Miller I like know what
you intend to do about Mildred. I got to
expect me to do but I figure to take
care of her humanity you know I. I'm not
admitted. I might. Even
want. All
the same I feel like you know what you
intend to do about me. I can do nothing one
man cannot solutions
a problem of the unmarried mother. Why
didn't you tell me. I just couldn't
have. Everything and be all right.
To. Do you still. Like me.
Really. Strange as it may seem I
always have. Because I was sure.
I did everything I could to make you
love me. I thought you were incapable of
loving anybody. Seems horrible to think
that you were willing to sacrifice
everything for that man I'm awfully sorry
for that. I should never forget you
wanted to.
Kill it if. You'd been found nice to me
I'll do anything he wants
will you why I want to
hear Oh do you.
They are angry.
And wish they have and then. There's
If you want me to. Cost that
nothing could let me know just
a man what I had everything ready. To
. Mean.
I may. Be.
Proud aren't Nora. I did you have to.
Just passing the. I wonder of
my nose against you and oh.
My and I hear from you I was just going
to write. You come to think me. Well
I have been busy.
But you see. Nora. I've got
a new strange to tell you. You've
been so good to me to make you.
Feel it but. I'm sorry it was just over.
Mean you don't care for me anymore.
I'm afraid to. One of my down nothing
you've been wonderful to me. Is just that I
have. Been caught I knew I
knew you never love me as much and every
person presidents usually. Is usually one
who loves. One who is about
zero dollars the same. You want
a man to be nice to you you have to be
rough in the here and. You create a man on
a scale.
That someone else. Yes.
The issue. Mildred. She's coming.
After all she. How could.
Anyone I like to know.
Just the way you were found
her in some way. You. Die and
you. Wish she was you know.
As every human being is.
Something rather.
Funny looking at a bank isn't it
a can't believe it's mine
now if you'll excuse me. So
glad it's over darling even so good
to me now on things to be different
now you will take good care
of her well that I will moan.
Good day good day. And.
Now you don't like it. Caught me off I'm
going to work all right there's not
a big Xango over on Sundays to see the
babies properly taken care of I will.
Do this afternoon. To come over and teach.
And well I know you find amusing and
I am always afraid of boring in.
Iowa Oh sorry I'm late.
I had to get rid of
a go why did you break up or why not
interested in my girl I'm only interested in
other men. You know like me.
A. Really I'm too hungry to know but
I think I like your art. I like you
a lot more they got him to take it up innit
and I and if you do I'll tell you some
funny stories no luck I'm thinking having
a wonderful time he did
for pay the bill. I'm
. Really not.
That bill. I'm sorry I probably
would have been better.
I mean. I'm not I'm not.
I'm. Helping the family I'm better.
Yet I want my money and.
Could not get it and not.
Just a moment. I would love
a Mildred but I. Know that
you've been there Bunny about
why my dear I don't know you are because
meds you have you got so many women don't
take Mildred with me but my dear old boy
she is nothing to me at all Oh nothing I
told.
Him that much Cannot you think you.
Think. You have taken
a good its last night.
I was not natural. I'm
in love with you. While to me well
grievous is good looking is amusing
it is the kind of things that make you laugh
I thank you not to make fun of me you
know it does appear you mean
a fine young man over here has noted I
was making fun of you when you said your
activity here you don't think it is and you
don't even know because group it isn't
in love with you how do you
know I asked him not to read
a letter I mean this morning
I've been up all night thinking
about you and I just sent
a special messenger who take this to you
in the door on your new notion of the time
I had with your friend last night kept
asking me if I love you and of course what
could I say doctors tell you this
so I'm making sure that you.
Help if I'm not him can I know I suppose
not but what you going on about nothing
only I was fool enough to think
that you cared for me I do.
Not know any other way but you do get
a grip it's in the other
way but you know you're of
a code that that sort of thing doesn't
mean anything to you that's what you think
.
It's no use going on about Philip said
yourself I couldn't help it if I'm in love
with him
well if there's anything else
to be said say it that's
a nice dress you haven't needed I
couldn't afford it but I paid for it you
have a nice apartment I couldn't
afford it but I paid for it you're
a gentleman you think you know what you've
done for me and if you think it matters
to me whether I'm a
gentleman or not if I were
a gentleman you don't suppose I'd care for
a cheap little. I'm sorry.
I don't want in this
way. Harry is waiting for me what do
you intend to do when I
going to Paris get out
out get.
I've moved three times and it's trying
this woman out of me down. I don't like to
do this but I thought I'm in the wrong.
Long live it down day here come on up.
In.
Looking at midnight all washing up and I
have an. Excuse me I'm doing the ward.
Anything interesting K. I was just thinking
what an unusual name you have for sale
you went through the days right
in the crossfire state having
a charity hospital my father lived far
we've been and. How the mighty know
full. Well father.
Get it is my daughter christened. A
mother always told us Sally is young man
is. Nice to me and was I mean use money
might be nice to you now father.
Fathers particular thing wrong and
think it's fun to investment it is.
Whether to try timed i Pad I will if I get
the job you should have you know coming
to see is the past Sunday.
Oh yes please do.
Explain how. You. Can patient behind give
me aht I've got nine children on
a Friday on bank three going
back. And with great admiration.
So I bring the air right now again the
sooner the better. I hope you didn't have
a haven here in my town I've been I have
had to know that is definitely true oh no
I always take meals by myself I like Vicente
cast. I don't think women orders to
dot
a table with me but don't you why
not it ruins conversation. I'm from
a very bad which I guess in their
head and women are never I.D.D.
Themselves when they have
an idea you sound like
a voice of old England I'm sorry I mean
she's finally got up put in the give me
strength to carry on. Not stop getting I'm
not jumping jack every time she comes
into the room she don't want you to make
a fuss about do you Sally if you want to
be rude if you sit still like she waits on
you don't get
a hang for Hillary we're sad now. You
speak quietly while I knew young man was
a bully. And if. You know
what I'm talking about how
many. Couldn't you still crap. There
Sam I channel you make I hear
better get Philip some more.
You stand anything better than English.
That is Tank God Simple pleasures good
appetite rich people. I was married to
a lady one. Would have.
Never met anything.
Really way because a lady has
a point of view what pass not
a tear in an individual at all to W.A.
How do you or do you want
to wife who going to cook
a dinner on your killed don't you think so
sad I don't think you mean Think Up and
down to where it's clean fun now Sally
wait on me I wait on you take my. Plan I
put you in
a young man's And she. What
do you think of that you
don't know what this means
to me. I think you never had
a family and this is almost the only place
I've ever known that had the quality of
. Home don't you think went
to queer. Everyone's queer
but me and the and sometimes the queer.
It's no use moaning no can't say.
That they never have kids is
a gentle one Adelaide D.D.
Had twice. He was asked me again to. Go
like yourself why don't
you come to accounting.
Gimmick.
Me I. Am up to date you mean
you know me. Too late you
know child. Don't get
ever know that.
Did you hear what I said Oh
man. Guess. I brought up
a painful subject and I thought you'd be
interested to hear about it so I just had
to bedtime I gave all I could that
you know me or don't. I thought
that you want to I can do
anything. I don't blame you
I would've told you only asked
me to give you the address. Of
a job I can tell you that they have you
around and asking for something to eat you
have the baby with her they're not
difficult to imagine the next.
Baby Alright I'm very grateful
to you and I can afford it I
get in your face either and as it is you're
welcome to my room I don't know what
will become of me and baby. Taken to
see him oh you know got on I expect.
A beginning to be well you
can have how you felt.
Let's not talk about
a jelly I don't like that
now OK Mildred I have no
misunderstanding about this the reason
you're here is because. Your wants not to
want to. Hear. Least I can
cook for you and keep you. Maybe
some day. You feel better about me
and I think the doctor used to be.
Oh thanks. I'll smoke it later. Well.
Good night night.
Man.
Man not enough to handle while ago she
said Miss Carey she said how can just
get by what's the matter with him
get into the stuff thing I calls
it have joys of making people about
you want to know what I think a half
a mile take them down the self.
You do nothing of the kind
I love those pictures Mildred I love
them for what they were meant to be.
And.
What happened to it.
When you still love me.
Oh I don't know. I was just going to
throw up and so my. Bad but didn't make.
Nothing on me. And how you got when
I was to come to. Me that way.
To me. Now what is that.
Where war.
Where. Where in.
Union.
He's not up at night.
Yeah oh.
And you. Knew. He'd.
Be
a. Union. You
.
Have way. F.
On it but you're doing up I couldn't flee.
And you better put on something
warmer so will be all right.
After
a. While. People
are not. Kids are
completely that. Keep it up
you're making
a fool of yourself to me feel pity. I
can't get all this. Nonsense you
have any way to go stay here as long
as you like with
a definite understanding you
despise us me me
I discussed you you yell your to my
you're not of me but just
on your own not looking at
a naked female Mildred you. Just use
why I'm going to care for you not what
I was always making up to not your bored
me stick by hey did you hit me made me
sick when I had like you kissed me I only
did it because you are big and me and
told me quite
a bit you'll get me Oh you're so
white my mouth why. I made up
for it let me can I don't know. That
just. Doesn't mean that you're the
guy you want I just. Want you
want you give me like months.
oh Oh
. You know now.
Well hit. Me that.
You want to be.
OK. Because.
They're leaving why. A man is
going what you intend to do.
Anything. Before you go out in the world
into the field trying to do something
about that for. Feeling good.
I know better tomorrow.
Are you going to I'm or at telling
me I would be well. Let's
try telling.
Me email. Me
a. Medium you'll.
Know meeting right now to get
a call which will nothing today.
Or experience. Nothing today all
the burden to know that you were
there. Not having nothing nothing
having that in.
The end
a. A A. A A
A A. A A
A bunch of interferes I know I.
Do. Well you you've been putting
on weight I'm sure you have and
why you say that the way you. Know the
name I look for it is more than men
and since you're not in our family and
when you didn't answer I went down to your
room you know the landlady said
she had to put you out. How do
you put it.
Followed by
a period signal my daughter just communicated
to me confirmation of our fish as you
know I've been on the beach most of my life
in fact in die here I was president of
the beach combers Union and as such an
inquiry and your image of standing. Where
have you been stay. Oh. Anywhere
Why did you come here post modest.
Stop being an English when
a man Don is out of time he came down
to well we want you here with us but I.
Thank you very much but I don't talk to.
Stay out till you get your back and I
won't know if I can talk about
it it's all really. Well.
Well here goes my amateur standing. I
really have no place to go. Till the
good of your monsoons you know ours is
completely on Saturday you'll probably wind
up with time fall duty you're not even on
I want to talk well I very much you have
but I must say I'm sick and
tired of sobbing Not at all.
And that too because of him I.
Wouldn't be having I cannot be out. Very
you know going to be jolly having you here
I hope I shan't have to stay very long you
do why I can't go on like this you know
I need a job my father
one that isn't much of
a love. So that on two. And father had
a job for you as he where where you work.
In Union.
The again the mean
mean. I was
right. All you know when down.
And you can't back. That.
Up had. Had you know.
That fate and I go to
a doctor will it be off hand all
day and stand there and me.
But instead of trouble
well I call. You a devil of
a dipshit. He's
not and I think.
He. Was the baby she died.
Long. Ago you might say I
thought I'm not I'm very
glad that I can help in that.
Technique make it up and
not be just chalk it up
a notch. And then I got you and I'm in
a pub with your. Yard and.
Tell me what I have and the.
Things you need. To.
Larry.
Let me. Play and.
Then.
I am.
I last day. By Sally.
Darling. I have a third
term and that you see. With
a sweet. Care because I'm going
away. I suppose in the food to
care but. It doesn't mean you have to do
anything about it. You can't help but just
because someone loves you and you don't
have that. One telling of the name.
Darling. Do you think you'll
always be like this about me in.
A minute to the first time you came
to our home. Thought it best that.
I meant something to you to approach
you when you do. The when I
come back if you still feel the
same when you marry me down.
The road don't you mean if you
still feel the same do you know.
What your life goal in ARE WE
ARE THEY COME ON not be create
a get out of. And I don't
want and I know that I am.
I understand is an interesting case look
at Omer don't go in there why not if you
please no you.
I'm going to carry on
you're not I'm not going.
To my wife. And you can to marry me.
Right away. Thank you. Baby.
Don't you make me what I am.
Why. Did you tell me another
Jeff to. Marry an ass and you
didn't just pick. Up that much
better than to know.
Her.
Get
a sudden but never never go back to
the day. I had to be realized that. I
had been beaten on the stand all those
years that I didn't escape. Because I was
limping through life. No thank you.
Because I was never the that's It was
incredible to me. That.
I'm not living anymore.
Because everything that's beautiful to
me is right here. Are two peas marry me.
If you know that there's
a lot. No one helped
a. Lot
about it. Yet.
For. Me.